One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Admiral Kizaru has made landfall!
الأميرال كيزارو اخترق صفوف العدو
The enemy has mobilized!
ترقبوا تحركات العدو
Don't let them fire those lasers!
لا تدعوهم يطلقوا الليزر
Attack!
أطلقوا
– It's a weaponized sea beast!
إنها وحوش البحر المسلحة
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
The weaponized sea beasts are attacking!
وحوش البحر المسلحة يأتونا تواليًا
We're in trouble!
يا للمصيبة
We've gotta take them down before they sink us!
فلنبادرهم قبل أن يهاجمونا
Leave it to me!
أنا لها
Steam Knuckle!
بُرجمة البخار
Forget the ships!
انسوا أمر السفن
You're dealing with me!
فإني لكم بالمرصاد
The vice admirals have landed, too!
نواب الأميرالات هبطوا الجزيرة
Which lab are they holding the Cipher Pol agents in?!
أين المختبر المحتجز داخله عملاء السايفر بول؟
The one up there.
هناك
In the Labophase...
...في المختبر
The Marines and the robot sea beasts...
البحرية والوحوش الآلية
just started fighting at the shore!
اندلع بينهم قتال على الساحل
As long as Sentomaru is commanding the pacifista,
،ما دام سينتومارو يقود الباشيفيستا
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
تسلسل السيطرة على الباشيفيستا
Five Elders
الشيوخ الخمسة
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites)
فيغابانك (ستيلا والأقمار)
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
Authority Chip
شريحة السلطة
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
تسلسل السيطرة على الباشيفيستا
Five Elders
الشيوخ الخمسة
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites)
فيغابانك (ستيلا والأقمار)
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
Authority Chip
شريحة السلطة
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
تسلسل السيطرة على الباشيفيستا
Five Elders
الشيوخ الخمسة
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites)
فيغابانك (ستيلا والأقمار)
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
Authority Chip
شريحة السلطة
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
تسلسل السيطرة على الباشيفيستا
Five Elders
الشيوخ الخمسة
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites)
فيغابانك (ستيلا والأقمار)
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
Authority Chip
شريحة السلطة
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
تسلسل السيطرة على الباشيفيستا
Five Elders
الشيوخ الخمسة
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites)
فيغابانك (ستيلا والأقمار)
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
Authority Chip
شريحة السلطة
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
تسلسل السيطرة على الباشيفيستا
Five Elders
الشيوخ الخمسة
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites)
فيغابانك (ستيلا والأقمار)
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
Authority Chip
شريحة السلطة
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
تسلسل السيطرة على الباشيفيستا
Five Elders
الشيوخ الخمسة
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites)
فيغابانك (ستيلا والأقمار)
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
Authority Chip
شريحة السلطة
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
تسلسل السيطرة على الباشيفيستا
Five Elders
الشيوخ الخمسة
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites)
فيغابانك (ستيلا والأقمار)
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
Authority Chip
شريحة السلطة
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
تسلسل السيطرة على الباشيفيستا
Five Elders
الشيوخ الخمسة
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites)
فيغابانك (ستيلا والأقمار)
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
Authority Chip
شريحة السلطة
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
تسلسل السيطرة على الباشيفيستا
Five Elders
الشيوخ الخمسة
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites)
فيغابانك (ستيلا والأقمار)
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
Authority Chip
شريحة السلطة
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
تسلسل السيطرة على الباشيفيستا
Five Elders
الشيوخ الخمسة
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites)
فيغابانك (ستيلا والأقمار)
Sentomaru
سينتومارو
Authority Chip
شريحة السلطة
the island's defenses are impenetrable!
يُفترض أن دفاع الجزيرة منيع
Isn't that why he showed up?! To take out Sentomaru?!
أتظنون أنه أتى للتخلص من سينتومارو؟
Kizaru?!
كيزارو؟
He's here already?!
هل وصل؟
No way!
غير معقول
He's fighting right below us as we speak!
إنهم يتقاتلون في الأسفل الآن
Kizaru, huh?
كيزارو إذًا؟
This brings back some unpleasant memories from Sabaody Archipelago...
رؤيته تقلّب مواجع ما حدث في أرخبيل شابوندي
Too bad. You guys are toast.
لن تلبثوا أن تموتوا
No way! Fighting Kizaru, of all people...
لا يُعقل، أما غير كيزارو يقاتله؟
I'm sorry, Sentomaru!
سامحني يا سينتومارو
What a heartbreaking battle!
بئس الذريعة التي تجبرك على قتاله، لن ألومك إن فررت
Keep your chin up, Stella!
روح عن نفسك يا ستيلا
For now, just focus on cracking the passcode!
صب اهتمامك على كشف رمز المرور في الوقت الراهن
Edison is right!
إديسون محق، فلنعجل
Okay!
أصبتما
Just surrender!
...يستحسن أن تستسلم
Sentomaru!
!يا سينتومارو-كن
Sacred Yasakani Jewel.
جوهرة الفاصلة المقدسة
I'm sorry, Unc!
اعذرني يا عم
Straw Hat Luffy and I made a promise!
لكني قطعت وعدًا لقبعة القش
Straw Hat?
قبعة القش؟
Since when do you side with pirates?
متى صرت توالي القراصنة؟
I'll work with anyone...
...سأتعاون مع أي أحد
who helps the man that saved my life escape this island!
إن كان يعين منقذ حياتي على الهرب من الجزيرة
How odd.
عجيب
They asked us to hunt bears, but...
ألم نُكلف نحن بصيد الدببة؟
Did that child beat us to it?
هل هزمهم الصبي؟
I hate the weaklings that live in the village!
أهل قريتي ضعفاء فلم أحتملهم
I'm never going back!
لن أرجع إليهم ثانيةً
They kicked you out, huh?
هل نفوك؟
I'm so tough, I don't even get hungry!
أنا قوي فلا يقرصني الجوع
But I wanna work!
لكني أريد عملًا
I want money!
فإني أحتاج المال
Oh, you have something you'd like to buy?
أمن شيءٍ تريد شرائه؟
Rice balls!
كرات الأرز
You were such a cute kid...
كم كنتَ لطيفًا
Work?
عمل؟
You seem pretty confident in your physical strength.
باديةٌ عليك ثقتك بقوتك البدنية
Say, kid, how would you like to be my bodyguard?
أتريد أن تكون حارسي الشخصي يا فتى؟
Are you gonna hire me?!
هل تقدم لي عملًا؟
I'll do it!
أقبله
Unc! Unc!
يا عم، يا عم
You mean me?
أتعنيني؟
Unc!
يا عم
How should I protect Old Man Punk?
كيف ليَ أن أحمي العجوز بانك؟
Unc?
أقلت «عم»؟
Do I look old enough to be an uncle?
ما زلت في ريعان شبابي
I want you to teach me, Unc!
علِّمني يا عم
I did my best to teach you, Sentomaru.
بذلت كل جهدي في تعليمك يا سينتومارو-كن
Ashigara Dokkoi!
الوهز بالثقل
But...
،لذا
my defense...
...فإن دفاعي
is as strong as yours.
لن يخسر أمامك...
Pacifista.
أيها الباشيفيستا
Your commander is unconscious, so there will be a change of plans.
من كان له الأولوية عليكم فقد وعيه وتغيرت الخطة
Assist the Marine ships against the weaponized sea beasts.
تعاونوا مع سفن البحرية لإغراق وحوش البحر المسلحة
The pacifista's directive...
...تنسيق الباشيفيستا
has been overwritten.
تغير
Such a waste to sink them,
إغراقهم تبديد لمواردنا
but if we can keep only one, we choose the pacifista.
ولكن الأفضل لنا اختيار الباشيفيستا عليهم
Give me a full damage report...
ما الأضرار بالدقائق القليلة الماضية؟
of the last few minutes.
أبلغها لي
Yes, sir!
عُلم
Sentomaru is down!
هُزم سينتومارو
What?!
ماذا؟
Let's hurry and deactivate the defense system!
علينا التعجل بتعطيل النظام الدفاعي
Yeah!
أجل
We can't let Sentomaru's sacrifice be in vain!
إياكما أن تهدرا الوقت الذي وفره لنا سينتومارو
Forget it. I'm Vegapunk, too!
لا جدوى فيما تفعلون، فأنا أيضًا فيغابانك
Kizaru is light itself!
إن كيزارو الضوء ذاته
He can pass through the laser barrier!
يمكنه تجاوز حاجز الليزر
You mean he can just come right in?!
أتعني أنه يقدر على الدخول إلى هنا؟
Yes!
أجل
He totally wiped the floor with us once already!
أذلّنَا ذلًا قبل زمن
It's been a while...
مر وقت طويل
Straw Hat crew.
يا طاقم قبعة القش
Hurry up, hurry up!
أسرعوا أسرعوا
As soon as the barrier is down, we're outta here!
سنهرب حالما يُعطل الحاجز
So far, so good!
الأمور تجري بسلاسة
I'll just take the ship around back!
سأحمل السفينة إلى الخلف
Sounds good!
نعتمد عليكِ
Let's eat while we can.
فلنأكل قدر الإمكان
Yeah.
أجل
You can't fight on an empty stomach.
المرء لا يقاتل على معدة خاوية
You're eating now, of all times?
ما لكما تأكلان؟
We're gonna escape soon, guys!
نحن بصدد الهروب من هنا
Lilith! What's up with that?!
ما هذا يا ليليث؟
An emergency alarm?!
إنذار الطوارئ؟
Why?! I thought this place...
لماذا؟
was impenetrable!
حصينًا؟...
At any cost, protect:
:الأولوية في الحماية
The power plant.
محطة الطاقة
Punk Records.
سجلات بانك
York.
يورك
And ideally...
وإن كانت لي الخيرة لحميت صاحبًا قديمًا
but alas...
...ولكن للأسف
At any cost, eliminate:
:الإبادة لازمة لما يلي
Dr. Vegapunk.
الدكتور فيغابانك
Kizaru made it inside the dome!
كيزارو اقتحم القبة
Luffy and the others are out there!
ولوفي والآخرين بالخارج
That can't be good. Luffy!
!ورطة عويصة، لوفي-سان
Tell them through the snail!
أبلغهم بحلزون الاتصال حالًا
Luffy! Run!
اهربوا يا لوفي
Until the ship is in place,
لن يُعطل الحاجز حتى ننتهي من نقل السفينة
Stussy!
ستوسي
Stussy?!
!ستوسي-تشان
Nami, I'm borrowing this!
سأستعيره يا نامي-سان
Sheesh! What gives?!
تبًّا، ما هذا؟ مسدس فقاعات؟
Looks like he forgot about you!
يبدو أن صاحبك تخلى عنك
So you got backup and thought you could make your move?!
هل اغتررت بنفسك لأن حليفك جاء؟
Between Kizaru and me,
بوجودي أنا وكيزارو
all of you are dead!
ستهلكون جميعًا
Don't underestimate us!
!لا تستخفنا
No wonder their ship wasn't at the shore.
لهذا لم أجد سفينتهم عند الساحل
It was here all along!
فقد كانت بالأعلى هنا
Hurry up!
بسرعة
Kizaru?! He's a Marine admiral!
!كيزارو
What's the plan, Luffy?!
ما العمل يا لوفي؟
Where'd he go?!
أين ذهب؟
Hey, Luffy!
يا لوفي
Hey, long time no–
...أهلًا، طالت الغيـ
That's just bad manners.
يا لسوء آدابك
Kizaru!
كيزارو
Compared to two years ago...
...نحن أقوى بمئة مرة
we're a hundred times stronger!
!مما كنا عليه قبل عامين
The Previous Day Mary Geoise
اليوم السابق بماريجوا
He's finally reached the top!
أفلح في تسلقه أخيرًا
Invincible Slave Kuma has returned!
العبد المنيع كوما عاد
Soldiers, stop him!
أوقفوه حالًا أيها الجنود
What's he doing here?!
ما الذي يخطط إليه؟
Oh no!
هذا تعيس
We can't stop him!
لا نقدر عليه
Ursus Shock!
صدمة الدب
Such an insolent slave...
ما أنت إلا عبد
What do you think you're doing?
ما الذي تفعله؟
The other day it was the Revolutionary Army, and now this...
هاجمنا الجيش الثوري سابقًا والآن أنت
This destruction is unprecedented, Kuma!
لم يسبق لهذا الدمار مثيلًا قط يا كوما
F-Fleet Admiral Sakazuki...
المشير ساكازوكي
Worthless scum!
لا فائدة تُرجى منكم
You soldiers are completely useless!
إنكم لجنودٍ متقاعسين
Hey, Akainu!
يا أكاينو
I ordered lobster for dinner last night, but they said they were all out!
أمرتهم أن يعدوا الروبيان في عشاء البارحة لكنه لم يكن متوفرًا
That's never happened before!
لم يحدث هذا من قبل
What's happening to Mary Geoise's food supply?!
ماذا حل بمؤونة ماريجوا؟
Hey, that's not important right now!
هذا ليس وقت التشكي
I've just been injured!
فأنا مصاب
Kuma the Tyrant is a mere slave!
ما الطاغية كوما إلا عبدٌ الآن فأعدمه من فورك
The thing is, Kuma...
اسمع يا كوما
if we can't control you,
،إذا لم تكن تحت طوعنا
then we can't afford to have you on the loose.
فلن نترك شخصًا خطر مثلك حرًّا طليقًا
Your sense of self should have been erased.
يُفترض أن وعيك تلاشى
You're as good as dead already.
...حالك حال الجثة الهامدة
So where do you think you're going?!
فأين تخال نفسك ذاهبًا؟
Hellhound
كلب الجحيم
Hellhound!
مي غو
I didn't know you still bled like a man.
لم أعلم أنك ما زلت تنزف كالبشر
Hold it, Kuma!
مهلًا يا كوما
Bark all you want, but Kuma will never regain his sense of self.
مهما بكيتِ فلن يعود وعي كوما
He volunteered to be reborn as a weapon.
فقد تطوع بنفسه ليتحول إلى سلاح حربي
That's a lie!
كاذب
There's no way...
...تطوعه بنفسه
There's no way he chose that!
تطوعه بنفسه أمرٌ محال
He would never leave me behind!
فما كان ليتخلى عني
Hey! Where is Kuma?!
أين كوما؟
Don't tell me you let him get away!
أيعقل أنه أفلت منك؟
You're the fleet admiral!
!وهذا وأنت المشير
Where are you going?
أين عساه يذهب؟
You're just a puppet...
...وهو مجرد دمية
Present Day Egghead New World
اليوم الحاضر بإيغهيد بالعالم الجديد
without a mind or free will...
!لا وعي ولا إرادة له
Pacifista and all Marines, keep shooting!
واصلوا إطلاق النار يا جنود والبحرية وأيها الباشيفيستا
Destroy the weaponized sea beasts!
دمروا وحوش البحر المسلحة
Enter the Fabriophase! Occupy the island!
ادخلوا طابق المصنع واحتلوا الجزيرة
Admiral Kizaru has entered the Labophase above the clouds!
الأميرال كيزارو اقتحم طابق المختبر فوق الغيوم
Gum-Gum...
فاكهة المطاط
Black Mamba!
الثعابين السوداء
Now I see how you were able to defeat Kaido.
!كما هو متوقع من الرجل الذي هزم كايدو
You're quite the powerhouse.
!لستَ خصمًا سهلًا
However...
،ولكن
what would make a pirate like you want to protect Vegapunk?
لمَ يحاول قرصانٌ حماية فيغابانك؟
You tell me!
سؤالي من نفس المنطلق
Why do you guys wanna kill Apple Gramps?!
لماذا تحاولون قتل العجوز ذو التفاحة؟
It's not that I want to...
ما كان قتله رغبتي
How far is he going?!
إلى أي مدى سيطير؟
I don't want to kill him.
ما كان قتله رغبتي إطلاقًا
I've known Vegapunk for a long time...
عرفت فيغابانك منذ زمن طويل
so I'd appreciate it if you'd stay out of this.
لذا هلّا تكف عن اعتراض طريقي
Acceleration is power!
التسارع قوة
It's complete!
اكتمل
Its name is Vegaforce-01!
أسميته فيغافورس-1
The dream of man!
إنه حلم البشرية
A giant robot!
آلي عملاق
Luffy!
لوفي
What's going on?!
ماذا يحدث؟
I thought I was a goner!
حسبتني هلكت
Oh... Oh no!
ويلي
Franky! Bonney!
فرانكي، بوني
Lilith?!
ليليث؟
Run!
اهربا
The Vegaforce-01 is gonna...
....ففيغافورس-1
Just run!
اهربا فحسب
Damn it all!
سحقًا
The robot of our dreams, the Vegaforce-01...
دمر آلي أحلامنا فيغافورس-1
That jackass is gonna pay!
تبًّا، هذا لا يُغتفر
Is the Sunny alright?!
هل الساني سالمة؟
Hey! Straw Hat flew right through us!
تمهل، قذف بقبعة القش بعيدًا أيضًا
Kizaru, you bastard!
أيها الوغد يا كيزارو
Look how big you've gotten, Bonney...
كبرتِ كثيرًا يا بوني
Kids these days grow up so fast.
أطفال هذه الأيام ينضجون سريعًا
Are you still carrying a grudge?
لا شك أنكِ تحملين حقدًا
An order was issued to assassinate the man you hate, Dr. Vegapunk.
لدي أوامر بقتل الدكتور فيغابانك الذي تحتقرينه
Shut up.
اخرس
I have a new target in my crosshairs!
تغير هدفي
Age Skewer!
الزمن القاتل
Whoa.
ويحي
I'd prefer...
...لا تجبريني
not to hurt any acquaintances outside the scope of my mission.
أن أمس معارفي بسوء ما لم أؤمر بذلك
No! Not that way...!
...مهلًا، إن هذا الاتجاه
Bonney!
بوني
That's it, Kizaru!
أيها الوغد كيزارو
Radical...
راديكال
Be–
...بيـ
Where'd he go?!
أين هو؟
He just vanished?!
أين اختفى؟
Stella's in danger!
ستيلا في خطر
Franky! Call them!
اتصل بهم يا فرانكي
Control Room Labophase
غرفة التحكم بالمختبر
Come in, control room!
أتسمعوني يا غرفة التحكم؟
Franky, are you okay?!
هل أنتم بخير يا فرانكي؟
We heard a big explosion over there!
سمعنا دوي انفجار ضخم من جهتكم توًّا
That you, Usopp? Is everyone alright?!
أهذا أنت يا أوسوب؟ هل الجميع بخير؟
What? Y-Yeah...
أ-أجل
Good to hear! So he's not there yet.
ارتحت، لم يصل بعد
What do you mean?
من تقصد؟
Eureka!
نجحنا
The deactivation code for the defense system...
...رمز تعطيل نظام الدفاع
– ...is cracked!
!توصلنا إليه
Really?!
حقًّا؟
In your face, York!
موتي بغيظك يا يورك
Dammit! You smart-asses!
تبًا لكم أيها العباقرة المزعجين
Franky, we can bring down the barrier at any time!
فرانكي-كن، باستطاعتنا تعطيل الحاجز متى أردنا
Did you move the Vegaforce-01 and the ship to the back?!
هل نقلتم السفينة بفيغافورس-1 إلى الخلف؟
No, because...
...بشأن هذا
What a pity.
للأسف الشديد
Your escape plan has failed.
باءت خطة هروبك بالفشل
Vegapunk.
يا فيغابانك
K-K-Kizaru!
!كـ-كـ-كيزارو
When did you get here?!
متى دخل إلى هنا؟
Wh... Wh-Wh-Wh-Why?!
لـ-لـ-لـ-لماذا؟
What happened to Luffy?!
ماذا حلّ بلوفي؟
We're done for...
انتهى أمرنا
So it was you who caused that explosion?
هل الانفجار الذي حدث توًّا من صنيعك؟
Yeah...
أجل
Unfortunately...
للأسف الشديد
your giant dream robot...
...آلي الأحلام العملاق
was blown to smithereens.
فجرته
What?!
ماذا؟
Hogwash!
غير معقول
I hope you understand...
تفهم أرجوك
This is very difficult for me, and I'd rather not draw it out.
هذه مهمة عسيرة علي فلا أريد إطالتها
What is it?!
ما الأمر؟
What?! What?!
ماذا يحدث؟
What is it this time?!
ما الأمر الآن؟
What?!
ماذا؟
Phew, that was spicy!
كان هذا ساخنًا
There you are.
ها هي ذي
So this must be...
...أهذه
Nice try knocking me all the way down!
أحسنت ركلي إلى الأسفل
I thought going through the barrier twice was gonna kill me for sure!
!عبرتُ الحاجز مرتين، حسبتني هلكت